

CA. SAMPADA BHAGVAT

- Vishal Nagar, Pimple Nilakh, Pune, India 411027
- +91 9881241318
- casampadabhagvat@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Chartered Accountant with 5 years of experience in accounting and taxation and Having 1 years of Experience SAP FI/CO functional consulting with 1 Implementation (Rollout) with supporting Projects.

Excellent verbal and written communication skills and the ability to communicate effectively with both non-technical business users and technical IT developers.

EDUCATION

Henry Harvin Education, New Delhi, DL, 2022 SAP FICO POWER USER PROGRAMME: Accounting

INSTITUTE OF CHARTERED ACCOUNTANTS OF INDIA, New Delhi, DL, 2020 CHARTERED ACCOUNTANT: Accounting, Taxation & Finance

Member of Institute of Chartered Accountants of India

PUNE UNIVERSITY, SP COLLEGE, PUNE, 2013

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE: ACCOUNTING, TAXATION AND COSTING

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- SAP FICO ECC 6.0 and SAP FICO \$4 Hana
- Tally Prime 2.1
- Microsoft Word and Microsoft Excel
- Accounting and bookkeeping
- Payment processing

- Financial statement analysis
- Tax management
- General ledger accounting
- A/P and A/R reconciliations

EXPERIENCE

CHARTERED ACCOUNTANT, 05/2023 - Current

Sagar Lahane and Company, Chartered Accountant, Pune, India

- 1. Monitored Accounting of various Individuals and companies.
- 2. Responsible for Filling of Income Tax Returns for Individual Residents, NRI
- 3. Responsible for Initial meeting till finalization of ITR
- 4. Planned and worked methodically and efficiently to continually meet strict financial deadlines.
- 5. Produced and reviewed personal and corporate taxation works with exceptional accuracy and efficiency
- 6. Prepared and reviewed accounts with meticulous precision for various sole traders and partnerships.

7. Coordinated month-end closing processes to ensure completion ahead of aggressive deadlines.

ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT, 02/2022 - 04/2023

Connecting Roots IT Consulting & Services, Pune, Maharashtra

- Configured the IMG settings as demanded by the Client business process requirements.
- Define the Organizational Structure and global parameters (chart of accounts, account groups, fiscal year variant, posting period Variant, field status variant, document types and OBY6 Settings), creation of the GL masters & define number range intervals for sample documents & customization of accrual and deferral documents.
- Creation of customer and vendor account groups.
- Responsible for FI-GL, AR, AP, BA and AA.
- Created house bank and bank master data and bank reconciliation configuration and Bank Reconciliation Statement.
- Configuration automatic payment program.
- Configuring asset accounting, integration with GL through account determination, screen layout for asset masters, depreciation areas and depreciation keys.
- Configuring financial statement version (FSV) as per the client requirements.
- Uploading master data (GL, vendors, customers, assets) through LSMW.
- Configuration of Withholding Taxes and Taxes on Sales/Purchases.
- Preparation of documents and provided the training to end user.
- Generate Financial Statements like Profit and loss account, Balance Sheet.
- Analyze issues and provide resolution Solving of maintenance Issues in the area of G/L, A/P, A/R.
- Training the users and troubleshooting day-to-day issues for FI module transactions.
- Resolved User issues on timely basis.
- Making configuration changes as required by the business.

DEPUTY MANAGER, 10/2021 - 01/2022

ICICI Bank, Pune

- Appraise /underwrite the loan
- Manage the entire credit application process, right from login to disbursement
- Manage post disbursement documents and partly disbursed cases
- Co-ordinate with legal, technical, Fl and Risk Containment Unit agency for processing the file / docket and Responsible for TAT of delivering sanction letter and disbursement
- Understand and analyze the financial standing of the client while preparing the credit

DEPUTY MANAGER, 10/2020 - 09/2021

BVG India Limited, Pune

- Finalization of daily-accounts
- Preparation like Balance Sheet, P & L, fund flow statement (Monthly)
- Statutory & FDA Audit handling
- Review of monthly schedules of P&L and Balance sheet
- Co-ordination with other department like Production, Tax, GST, HR
- Stock Accounting and Management in Tally Software
- Analysis of Cost and Discount Policies
- · Reconciliation of all bank accounts on daily basis

Reconciliation of Receivables and Payable

ASSOCIATE, 11/2018 - 01/2020

Sagar Lahane & Co. Chartered Accountants, Pune

- Bank Audits (Statutory and Concurrent)
- GST registration and GST Returns
- Preparation of Income tax returns of Individuals and Private Limited Companies
- TDS deduction, deposit and returns
- Project Finance
- Accounting, Registration of Shop Act, MSME

.....

ARTICLE ASSISTANT, 06/2013 - 08/2016

BSMART & Associates LLP, Chartered, Pune, Maharashtra

- Project Finance
- Bank NPA Verification for Asset Management Company
- Preparation of Income-tax returns of Individuals, firms & corporate
- TDS deduction, deposit and returns Service Tax Returns (under earlier law)
- Conducted statutory audit of several private limited companies
- Tax audits of individuals, firms & corporate BSNL Internal Audit Accounting

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Marathi

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- DECLARATION: I hereby declare that the above Information given by me is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. Place:
- Signature CA. Sampada Bhagvat.